[__] I want to leave this town.
See the world with you.
Only angry looks and frowns. I don't
care when it's us, too.
Desert towns and a road cafes
boats upon a dash.
Cross the roads towards LA.
Forget about the past.
Let's leave in the morning.
We'll be on the internet.
Life around is boring.
Let's just get away. Hey,
we're on a oneway trip to
have I know
half a pack of cigarettes on an open
road.
I found that at 12:00
right hand on yours.
Once the radio cuts out, we'll roll the
door.
Let's leave in the morning.
We'll be on the interstate.
Laugh around this boring.
Let's just get away. Hey, let's leave in
the morning.
We'll be on the interstate.
Life around is boring.
Let's just get away. Hey.